某些东西把萨姆塑造成了怪物
Something turned him into a monster.
神秘的一串字母
Croatoan.
恶魔病毒？类似于恶魔病毒战争
A demonic virus? more like demonic germ warfare.
如果我们都感染怎么办？如果我们都步入疯狂？
What if we all have it? what if we all go crazy?
追述到1835年 萨姆埃尔 科尔特造了一把枪
Back in 1835, samuel colt made a gun.
传说这枪可以杀死一切
They say this gun can kill anything.
- 我是皮囊？- 你就是皮囊
- I'm a vessel? - You're the vessel.
你们得得到我得同意 米伽勒也一样
You need my consent. michael needs.
这一切都取决于我
my say-so to ride.
真不幸
Unfortunately, yes.
我回答不
The answer's no.
- 你明白我是谁 - 路西法
- You know who I am. - Lucifer.
你是被选中的 萨姆
You're the one, sam.
你才是我的皮囊
You're my vessel.
这一切不会发生的
That'll never happen.
- 我知道你相信我 - 那你怎么说？
- I know you don't trust me. - So, what are you saying?
我很危险
That i'm dangerous.
也许分道扬镳才是最好的方式
Maybe it's best we just go our separate ways.
伙计晚上好 准备放纵你的灵魂么
Hi. good evening, brother. is your soul rapture-ready?
谢谢 先生 愿上帝与你同在
Thank you, sir. god bless.
伙计晚上好 准备放纵你的灵魂么
Good evening, folks. is your soul rapture-ready?
我很愿意为你展示
Because what i'd like to do is just show you.
上帝的最爱的是你
Exactly what god's love is for you.
好吧 愿上帝与你同在
Okay, god bless.
不好意思 朋友 有没有时间考虑下
Excuse me, friend, but have you taken time out.
我们的上帝计划
To think about god's plan for you?
这很扯蛋 伙计
Too friggin' much, pal.
我们在说科尔特 对不对
We're talking about the colt, right?
我的意思是
I mean, as in the colt?
我们都是
We are.
这根本没意义
Well, that doesn't make any sense.
为啥恶魔要拿着这枪
I mean, why would the demons keep a gun around.
互相厮杀
That, uh, kills demons?
你说什么
What? what? did…
我听不见
I didn't … I didn't get that.
真好玩
You know, it's kind of funny,
我正在和上帝的邮差在通电话
Talking to a messenger of god on a cellphone.
就好比看坠天使骑摩托车
It's, you know, like watching a hells angel ride a mo-ped.
这不好玩 迪恩
This isn't funny, dean.
你前面说的我都没听见
The voice says i'm almost out of minutes.
好吧
Okay, all right.
我告诉你 卡西
I'm … i'm telling you, cass,
那群混蛋现在想熔了那把枪
The mooks have melted down the gun by now.
我听到的可不是这样
Well, I hear differently.
如果这是实事而且你仍继续想完成
And if it's true and if you are still set.
你那个白痴的猎杀恶魔任务的话
On the insane task of killing the devil,
我们就得这么干
This is how we do it.
好吧 要怎么做
Okay. where do we start?
你现在在哪里？
Where are you now?
堪萨斯城
Kansas city.
世纪旅馆 103房间
Century hotel, room 113.
我马上就到
I'll be there immediately.
我刚开了16个小时的车才到这里好不
I just drove like 16 hours straight, okay?
我可是活生生的人
I'm human.
我还有点事要做
And there's stuff I got to do.
什么事
What stuff?
吃饭还有睡觉
Eat, for example. in this case, sleep.
你得给我4个小时休息下 好吗
I just need like four hours once in a while, okay?
可以
Yes.
你可以明天一早出现在这里
Okay, so, you can pop in tomorrow morning.
我会的
Yes.
那我只能
I'll just …
等在这里
…wait here, then.
混蛋卡西 我要睡觉
Damn it, cass, I need to sleep!
是我 迪恩
Dean, it's me.
萨姆
Sam?
4点04分
Four past four.
以下内容很重要
This is important.
那么你是它的皮囊
So, you're his vessel, huh?
路西法进入你体内来和天使们大干一场
Lucifer's wearing you to the prom?
一点没错
That's what he said.
当你还认为你已经没有价值的时候
Just when you thought you were out,
它们又把你扯进来是不是 萨姆
They pull you back in, huh, sammy?
就这样
So, that's it?
你就这反映
That's your response?
你希望得到点什么 我不知道
What are you looking for? I don't know.
一点点慌乱 也许
A-a little panic, maybe?
我想我这个时候
I guess i'm a little numb.
对这个惊天动地的消息有点麻木了吧
To the earth-shattering revelations at this point.
你想怎么办
What do you want to do about it?
首先 我想重操旧业
I want back in, for starters.
- 萨姆 - 我说真的
- Sam. - I mean it.
我受够被这些狗娘养的摆布了
I am sick of being a puppet to these sons of bitches.
我想猎杀他
I'm gonna hunt him down, dean.
这么说来 我们又重新回到复仇之路了
Oh, so, we're back to revenge, then, are we?
聪明啊 瞧咱上次的复仇结果多好啊
Yeah, 'cause that worked out so well last time.
不是复仇
Not revenge.
是救赎
Redemption.
你的意思是 你就这样回来
So, what, you're just gonna walk back in.
我们又重新变成黄金搭档二人组
And we're gonna be the dynamic duo again?
迪恩 我能做到
Look, dean, I can do this.
真的 我会证明给你看
I can. i'm gonna prove it to you.
听着 萨姆
Look, sam…
无论我们怎么做
It doesn't matter…
都没有用
Whatever we do.
在这场末日决战中 我们一个是火
I mean, it turns out that you and me, we're the, uh…
另一个就是油
The fire and the oil of the armageddon.
就为了这个理由
You know, on that basis alone,
咱们也该各拣半个地球
We should just pick a hemisphere…
永远分开
Stay away from each other for good.
迪恩 不一定非得这样
Dean, it does not have to be like this.
- 我们可以抗争 - 没错
- We can fight it. - Yeah, you're right, we can.
但不是在一起抗争
But not together.
在一起时 我们并没有更强
We're not stronger when we're together, sam.
而是变弱了
I think we're weaker.
因为不管我们之间
Because whatever we have between us …
是爱 是亲情
Love, family, whatever it is …
他们总会利用这点来对付我们
They are always gonna use it against us.
你心知肚明
And you know that.
我们分开更好
We're better off apart.
我们说不定能避开路西法和米迦勒
We got a better chance of dodging Lucifer and Michael.
避开这整件事
And this whole damn thing…
只要我们不在一起
If we just go our own ways.
迪恩 不要这样
Dean, don't do this.
再见 萨姆
Bye, Sam.
末日
THE END.
小妹妹
Little girl?
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
你一声不吭 有点让我毛骨悚然呢
You know the not-talking thing is kind of creepy, right?
我靠
Oh, crap.
2014年8月1日
"August 1st, 2014."
收音有干扰 肯定没好事
That's never a good sign.
croatoan病毒登陆澳洲
"Croatoan pandemic reaches Australia."
我就知道 回到未来这种狗血剧情
I thought I smelled your stink.
跟你脱不了干系
On this "back to the future" crap.
佩林总统为轰炸休斯顿事件辩解
"President Palin defends bombing of Houston."
房地产业绝对是买方市场了
Certainly a buyer's market in real estate.
来看看体育界有什么新闻
Let's see what's happening in sports.
哦对了 没体育这回事儿了
That's right … no more sports.
因为国会撤销了集会权
Congress revoked the right to group assembly.
国会也是徒负虚名了
What's left of congress, that is.
要我说的话 不过剩个空架子了
Hardly a quorum, if you ask me.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我们被迫利用非常规资源 依靠一些
Afraid we had to tap some unorthodox resources of late …
恶魔眼线
Human informants.
我们还去找过一些
We've been making inspirational visits.
比较边缘的基督教团体
To the fringier Christian groups.
把你的照片给他们 让他们密切留意
They've been given your image, told to keep an eye out.
旅馆外那个圣经狂人
The bible freak outside the motel …
他向你打小报告了
He, what, dropped a dime on me?
前进 信徒精兵
Onward, Christian soldiers.
快送我回去 你个婊子养的
Now send me back, you son of a bitch.
你会回去的 等时机到了
Oh, you'll get back … all in good time.
我们想让你在这浸个三天
We want you to marinate a bit.
浸
Marinate?
三天
Three days, Dean.
三天时间 看看能不能扭转你的想法
Three days to see where this course of action takes you.
你这什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我的意思是 你的选择会带来相应的后果
It means that your choices have consequences.
如果你继续对米迦勒说不的话
This is what happens to the world.
世界就会变成这个样子
If you continue to say "no" to Michael.
好好看看吧
Have a little look-see.
鲍比
Bobby?
鲍比 我进来了喽
Bobby, I'm coming in!
人都跑哪去了
Where is everybody, bobby?
赤塔拉营地
"Camp Chitaqua."
不会吧
Oh, baby, no.
他们对你做了什么 我的爱车啊
Ohhh. Baby, what did they do to you?
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
你不觉得 该问这问题的是我吗
I should be asking that question, don't you think?
这样吧 给我一个理由
In fact, why don't you give me one good reason.
为什么我不该把你就地正法了
Why I shouldn't gank you right here and now?
因为那样你就是在伤害你自己
Because you'd only be hurting yourself.
您真幽默
Very funny.
听着
Look, man…
我不是什么变形人或者魔鬼
I'm no shapeshifter or demon or anything, okay?
我知道 趁你昏迷 我把驱魔术使了个遍
Yeah, I know. I did the drill while you were out.
银器 盐 圣水 都不管用
Silver, salt, holy water … nothing.
但有意思的是
But you know what was funny…
你身上藏着
Was that you had.
我的撬锁器 开箱器
Every hidden lockpick, box cutter, and switchblade.
和弹簧刀
That I carry.
想解释一下吗
Now, you want to explain that?
顺便解释一下 为什么你长得和我一摸一样
Oh, and the, uh…resemblance, while you're at it?
撒迦利亚
Zachariah.
你说什么
Come again?
我是2009年年末的你
I'm you from the tail end of 2009.
撒迦利亚把我拽下床
Zach plucked me from my bed.
扔到5年以后的未来
And threw me five years into the future.
他在哪 我想和他谈谈
Where is he? I want to talk to him.
我不知道
I don't know.
- 哈 你不知道 - 我的确不知道
- Oh, you don't know. - No, I don't know.
我只想回到我自己那一年
Look, I just want to get back to my own friggin' year, okay?
好
Okay.
如果你是我
If you're me…
说几件只有我才知道的事
Then tell me something only I would know.
朗达· 赫尔利
Rhonda Hurley.
我们当时是…19岁吧
We were, uh…19.
她让我们穿上她的内裤
She made us try on her panties.
内裤是粉色的
They were pink.
很光滑
And satiny.
而且…
And you know what?
我们还挺享受的
We kind of liked it.
没错
Touche.
你是说 撒迦利亚把你拽到这儿来
So, what … Zach zapped you up here.
看看事情变得多糟
To see how bad it gets?
大概吧
I guess.
Croatoan病毒 这就是他们的杀手锏
Croatoan virus, right? That's their endgame?
这种病毒高效 无药可医
It's efficient, it's incurable,
而且非常恐怖
And it's scary as hell.
它能把人变成怪物
Turns people into monsters.
两年前开始袭击主要城市
Started hitting the major cities about two years ago.
之后世界就一片狼藉
World really went in the crapper after that.
萨姆呢
What about Sam?
底特律生死之战
Heavyweight showdown in Detroit.
我想 萨姆没有撑下来
From what I understand, Sam didn't make it.
你当时没和他在一起
You weren't with him?
嗯
No.
我和萨姆在那之前 已经有…
No, me and Sam, we hadn't talked in…
5年没联系了
Hell, five years.
我们从来没去找他吗
We never tried to find him?
我有其他人要操心
I got other people to worry about.
你去哪
Where you going?
我得出去办个差
I got to run an errand.
就这样把我一个人扔在这儿吗？
Whoa. you're just gonna leave me here?
没错
Yes.
外面有一营担惊受怕的幸存者
I got a camp full of twitchy trauma survivors out there.
脑海中萦绕着世界末日的噩梦
With an apocalypse hanging over their head.
我可不想让他们看见
The last thing they need to see is.
这番诡异的情形
a version of "th.
所以你必须待在这儿
So, yeah, you stay locked down.
那好吧
Okay. all right. fine.
但你不用把我铐起来啊
But you don't have to cuff me, man.
拜托 你连自己都不信任吗
Oh, come on. you don't trust yourself?
对
No.
毫不信任
Absolutely not.
混蛋
Dick.
嗨 迪恩 你有空吗
Hey, Dean. you got a second?
不 哦是的 我想是吧
No. yes. uh…I-I guess.
嗨 恰克
Hi, chuck.
嗨
Hi.
听着 目前我们有充分罐头储备
So, uh, listen, we're pretty good on canned goods for now,
但其他的都已经用尽了
But we're down to next to nothing.
腐烂的食品…和卫生纸供应
On perishables and … and hygiene supplies.
人们可不喜欢这样
People are not gonna be happy about this.
你觉得我们该怎么办
So, what do you think we should do?
我也不清楚
I-i don't know.
或许…共享吗
Maybe, uh, share?
就像以色列集体农场那样的
You know, like at a kibbutz.
等等 你现在不是应该
Wait a minute. aren't you supposed.
正在出任务吗
to be out on a mission now?
当然啦 我这就去
Absolutely. and I will be.
老天！
Whoa! geez!
冷静点！小姐！
Easy, lady!
- 她叫芮莎 - 芮莎！
- Risa. - Risa.
你昨天整晚都在和简鬼混吧
You spent the night in jane's cabin last night, didn't you?
啥？有吗？我才没有
Uh, what? i-i don't … did i?
我原以为我们之间有过「一段情」呢
I thought we had a "connection."
当然啦
Well, i'm sure that we do.
是吗
Yeah?
- 嗨 芮莎 - 死远点
- Hi, risa. - Screw you.
老天 我差点就莫名其妙地
Oh, geez. i'm getting busted for.
成了冤大头
stuff I haven't done yet.
啥？
What?
算了
Uh, never mind.
恰克 那个…卡西还在吗？
Hey, Chuck, is…Cass still here?
在啊
Yeah.
我觉得他哪儿也不会去
I don't think cass is going anywhere.
好吧 这样来
So, in this way,
我们都是完形知觉中的一部分
We're each a fragment of total perception …
分成不同的隔间
Just, uh, one compartment.
由心灵之眼来洞察
In that dragonfly eye of group mind.
现在理解这完形知觉的关键在于
Now, the key to this total, shared perception …
出乎意料的物理现象
It's, um… it's surprisingly physical.
失陪了 女士们
Excuse me, ladies.
我想和我们无畏的领袖之间
I think I need to confer with our.
得进行一些商讨
fearless leader.
何不去沐浴放纵一下呢？
Why not go get washed up for the orgy?
你们都如此美丽
You're all so beautiful.
你这算啥？嬉皮士？
What are you, a hippie?
我以为你已经放弃给我归类的尝试了
I thought you'd gotten over trying to label me.
- 卡西 我们得谈谈 - 真奇怪
- Cass, we got to talk. - Whoa. Strange.
怎么了
What?
你…不是迪恩 不是现在的迪恩
You…are not you … not "now" you, anyway.
对！我不是 完全不是
No! yeah. yes, exactly.
你是哪一年来的？
What year are you from?
2009年
2009.
谁送你来的？撒迦利亚吗？
Who did this to you? is it zachariah?
是的
Yes.
有意思
Interesting.
是啊 真是相当的刺激
Oh, yeah, it's friggin' fascinating.
既然如此 你何不挥挥翅膀
Now why don't you strap on your angel wings.
把我送回去呢？
And fly me back to my page on the calendar?
我也想啊 挥挥翅膀
I wish I could just, uh, strap on my wings,
但是很抱歉 不成
But i'm sorry … no dice.
你喝醉了吗？
What, are you stoned?
通常来说…是的
Uh…generally, yeah.
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
凡人的生活就是如此
Life.
嘿！小心！
Hey. hey! watch out!
该死
Damn it.
我不想骗你们
I'm not gonna lie to you.
我和他之间的情况
Me and him …
很难解释清楚
It's a pretty messed-up situation we got going.
但是相信我
But believe me,
在必要情况下 我会将一切告知你们
When you need to know something, you will know it.
不过在那之前 我们还是个忙个的吧
Until then, we all have work to do.
你到底什么意思？
What the hell was that?
这句话该我问你吧！
你刚冷血地射死一个大活人
You just shot a guy in cold blood.
我们刚才在暴露的隔离区内
We were in an open quarantine zone …
撤离的时候被一群Crotes伏击
Got ambushed by some crotes on the way out.
Crotes就是Croatoan病毒感染者
Crotes … croatoans.
我们其中一个猎人感染上了病毒
One of them infected yager.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
经过这么多年后 我掌握了经验
'cause after a few years of this, I know.
一个半小时之后 我就能看出初步症状
I started seeing symptoms about a half an hour ago.
之后不久 他就会变异
Wasn't gonna be long before he flipped.
所以我一点也不觉得
I didn't see the point.
这有什么好让你感到良心不安的
In troubling a good man with bad news.
「良心不安」？
"troubling a good man"?
你当着自己人的面杀了他
You just blew him away in front of your own people.
难道你不觉得这会是人心惶惶吗
Don't you think that freaked them out a little bit?
现在可是2014年
It's 2014.
射死一只Crote 是再正常不过的事
Plugging some crote … it's called commonplace.
相比之下 和你在一起唧唧歪歪
Trading words with my friggin' clone …
这才会叫他们惶恐不安呢
That might have freaked them out a little.
好吧 听着…
All right, look …
不 该你听着
No, you look.
这是我的时代 不是你的
This isn't your time. it's mine.
轮不到你来发号施令 由我说了算
You don't make the decisions. I do.
所以我命令你乖乖呆着 你就得照办
So, when I say stay in, you stay in.
好吧 哥们 我很抱歉
All right, man. i'm sorry.
听着 我不想搞砸你…或者我…
Look, i-i'm not trying to mess you or…me …
我们两个的局面
Us up here.
我知道
I know.
这周末真是奇怪
It's just been a really wacky weekend.
和我说说
Tell me about it.
不管怎样 是什么任务
What was the mission, anyway?
科尔特
The colt?
是的
The colt.
它在哪
Where was it?
不处不在
Everywhere.
我们花了5年时间
They've been moving it around.
到处寻找
Took me five years, but…
我最终找到了
I finally got it.
而今晚
And tonight…
今晚 我要去干掉恶魔
…tonight, i'm gonna kill the devil.
所以 这就是科尔特枪吗
So, that's it? that's the colt?
如果有什么能杀死路西法 只有这把枪
If anything can kill Lucifer, this is it.
太棒了
Great.
我们已经找到路西法一些线索了吗
Have we got anything that can find lucifer?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我们 我们昨天在简的小木屋里
Oh, we were in, uh, Jane's cabin last night.
很显然 我们和芮莎谈过了
And, apparently, we and…risa have a connection.
你们闭嘴好吗
You want to shut up?
我们不必找路西法 我们知道他的方位
We don't have to find Lucifer. we know where he is.
我们上周抓的那个恶魔
The demon that we caught last week …
他是 他们的亲信之一
He was one of the…big guy's entourage.
他知道
He knew.
所以 一个恶魔告诉你撒旦的动向
So, a Demon tells you where satan's gonna be,
你就这么相信了
And you just believe it?
相信我 他没有撒谎
Oh, trust me … he wasn't lying.
你怎么知道
And you know this how?
我想 我们无畏的领袖
Our fearless leader, i'm afraid,
受过这方面的训练
Is all too well schooled in the art of getting to the truth.
严刑拷问吗
Torture?
所以 我们又开始用这招了
Oh, so, we're … we're torturing again.
那很棒 很经典
No, that's … that's good. classy.
我喜欢以前的你
What? I like "past you."
路西法在这儿
Lucifer is here.
现在 我了解这块儿地形
Now, I know the block and I know the building.
太好了 就在禁区中央
Oh, good … it's right in the middle of a hot zone.
到处都是僵尸 你说我计划太鲁莽了吗
Crawling with crotes, yeah. you saying my plan is reckless?
你是说 我们要直接走上马路
Are you saying we, uh, walk in straight up the driveway,
穿过所有的恶魔和僵尸
Past all the demons and the crotes,
- 然后一枪打死这恶魔吗 - 是的
- And we shoot the devil? - Yes.
如果你不喜欢「鲁莽」
Okay, if you don't like, uh, "reckless, "
我也许可以用「漫不经心」来形容
I could use "insouciant, " maybe.
你来不来
Are you coming?
当然
Of course.
为什么他 他是5年前的你
But why is he? I mean, he's you five years ago.
如果他出什么事 你也玩了 是吗
If something happens to him, you're gone, right?
他也去
He's coming.
好吧
Okay.
好了 我让大家准备起来
Well, uh… i'll get the grunts moving.
我们装备好武器 午夜出发
We're loaded and on the road by midnight.
好吧
All right.
为什么要带我去
Why are you taking me?
放松 你会没事的
Relax. you'll be fine.
撒迦会保护你 不是么
Zach's looking after you, right?
我不是那意思
No, that's not what I mean.
我要知道到底发生了什么
I want to know what's going on.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
你过来 我要给你看样东西
You're coming because I want you to see something.
我要你看看我们的兄弟
I want you to see our brother.
萨姆吗
Sam?
我以为他死了
I thought he was dead.
萨姆在底特律没死
Sam didn't die in Detroit.
他说了 「同意」
He said "yes."
「同意」吗
"Yes"?
等等
Wait.
你是说
You mean …
没错
That's right.
对恶魔说了
The big "yes."
「同意」俩字
To the devil.
路西法现在借由他的身体作恶
Lucifer's wearing him to the prom.
为什么他会这么做
Why would he do that?
希望我能知道
Wish I knew.
但现在我们别无选择
But now we don't have a choice.
它在他身体里也不会出来
It's in him, and it's not getting out.
现在我们要去杀他 迪恩
And we've got to kill him, Dean.
你要见证这一刻
And you need to see it …
这该死的一切 有多糟糕
The whole damn thing, how bad it gets …
所以你就能走不同的路
So you can do it different.
什么意思
What do you mean?
撒迦说 他会把你送回09年的 是么
Zach said he was gonna bring you back, right? to '09?
是
Yeah.
好 那你回去后
Well, when you get back home…
你要说「同意」
You say "yes."
听清楚吗 对米迦勒说「同意」
You hear me? say "yes" to michael.
那太疯狂了
That's crazy.
如果我让他附身 米迦勒就能战胜恶魔
If I let him in, then Michael fights the devil.
那会毁掉半个地球
The battle's gonna torch half the planet.
看看你周围 伙计
Look around you, man.
半个比没有好点
Half the planet's better than no planet,
我们现在就什么也没有
Which is what we have now.
如果能重来 我会立刻答应
If I could do it over again, i'd say "yes" in a heartbeat.
那为什么不呢 我试过了
So why don't you? i've tried!
我喊到岔气
I've shouted "yes" till I was blue in the face!
天使们都不搭理
The angels aren't listening!
他们只是 离开了 放弃了
They just…left … gave up!
对我来说太迟了 但对你
It's too late for me, but for you …
不 一定还有其他方法
Oh, no. there's got to be another way.
是的 我也是这么想的
Yeah, that's what I thought.
我太过自信
I was cocky.
从没想过我会失败
Never actually thought i'd lose.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
迪恩
Dean…
我大错特错
I was wrong.
我求你
I'm begging you.
答应吧
Say "yes."
但是你没答应
But you won't.
就因为我没有
'cause I didn't.
因为我不在09年 不是么
Because that's just not us, is it?
你真的是09年来的吗
So, you're really from '09?
是的 恐怕是的
Yeah, afraid so.
给你点忠告
Some free advice?
回到过去以后 记得囤积厕纸
You ever get back there, you hoard toilet paper.
懂吗 越多越好
You understand me? hoard it.
像囤金子一样囤积起来
Hoard it like it's made of gold.
因为现在它就是金子
'cause it is.
多谢了啊 恰克
Thank you, chuck.
你会感激我的 记住我的话
Oh, you'll thank me, all right. mark my words.
待会见
I'll see you around.
好的
Yeah.
好了
Okay.
让我看看
Let me see those.
你也想来点吗
You want some?
安非他明
Amphetamines?
极佳的醒酒药
It's the perfect antidote to that absinthe.
不要会错我的意思 卡西
Don't get me wrong, cass.
我
I, uh…
我很高兴看到你不再愁眉苦脸
I'm happy that the stick is out of your ass,
但是
but…
嗑药 酗酒 还有爱情导师那套
What's going on … w-with the drugs.
到底发生了什么事
And the orgies and the love-guru crap?
有什么好笑的
What's so funny?
我不再是个天使了 迪恩
Dean, i'm not an angel anymore.
什么
What?
是的 我坠入凡间了
Yeah, I went mortal.
什么意思 出了什么事
What do you mean? how?
我猜和其他天使的离开
I think it had something to do.
有关
with the other.
当他们逃跑的时候
But when they bailed,
我的魔力就就好像
My mojo just kind of…
枯竭了
Shhrr! … drained away.
而现在 我就是一个普通的凡人
And now, you know, i'm practically human.
我是指 迪恩 我毫无用处
I mean, dean, i'm all but useless.
去年 摔断了腿
Last year, broke my foot.
卧床了修养两个月
Laid up for two months.
这么说来 你是个凡人了
So, you're human.
欢迎加入凡人俱乐部
Well, welcome to the club.
多谢
Thanks.
只是我曾经属于一个更高级的俱乐部
Except I used to belong to a much better club.
而现在我魔力全无
And now i'm powerless…
一个毫无希望的可怜虫
I'm hapless, i'm hopeless.
我是指 为什么我他妈的
I mean, why the hell not bury myself.
不沉溺在女人和颓废中呢
In women and decadence, right?
这就是世界末日
It's the end, baby.
颓废就是为这准备的
That's what decadence is for.
为什么不在死前好好享乐一番呢
Why not bang a few gongs before the lights go out?
但是
But, then…
那只是我的方式
That's just how I roll.
那 第二层的窗户
There. second-floor window.
我们从那里进去
We go in there.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
他们绝对看不到我们
They'll never see us coming.
相信我
Trust me.
现在检查武器 五秒倒计时行动
Now, weapons check. we're on the move in five.
嘿 我
Hey, uh…me.
能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a sec?
告诉我到底怎么回事
Tell me what's going on.
什么
What?
我了解你
I know you.
你在对这些人对我撒谎
You're lying to these people and to me.
是吗
Is that so?
是的
Yeah.
我知道你撒谎时的表情
See, I know your lying expressions.
我在镜子里看到过
I've seen them in the mirror.
你有什么事瞒着我们
Now, there's something you're not telling us.
我不知道你到底在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
是吗
Oh, really?
那好 我似乎不是你的队伍中
Well, I don't seem to be the only member.
唯一一个有疑心的人吧
of your posse wit.
那么 也许我去问问他们
So, uh, maybe i'll just take my doubts over to them.
好吧 等等
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. wait.
什么
What?
仔细看看周围 伙计
Take a look around you, man.
这个地方应该塞满了僵尸
This place should be white-hot with crotes.
但是你有看见了吗
Where are they?
他们给我们让了一条道
They cleared a path for us.
意味着这完全是
Which means that this is…
一个陷阱
A trap … exactly.
那我们就不能从前面进了
Well, then we can't go through the front.
的确 我们不会
Oh, we're not.
他们会
They are.
他们就是诱饵
They're the decoys.
你和我 我们从后面进
You and me … we're going in through the back.
你是指 你要把你的朋友们
You mean you're gonna feed your friends.
送入虎口吗
Into a meat grinder?
甚至卡西
Cass, too?
你想用他们的死来
You want to use their deaths.
分散路西法的注意力吗
As a diversion?
伙计 你脑子烧坏了吗
Oh, man, something is broken in you.
你这是我永远不会做出的决定
You're making decisions that I would never make.
我不会平白牺牲我的朋友
I wouldn't sacrifice my friends.
的确 你不会
You're right. you wouldn't.
事实上 这正是我们如今
It's one of the main reasons.
陷入困境的主要原因
we're in this mess, actually.
这些人依靠你 信赖你
These people count on you. they trust you.
他们相信我会杀死恶魔拯救世界
They trust me to kill the devil and to save the world,
而那正是我要去做的
And that's exactly what i'm gonna do.
不 不会的 我不会让你去的
No. not like this, you're not. i'm not gonna let you.
是吗
Oh, really?
是的
Yeah.
迪恩 你好
Hello, dean.
你真是个惊喜啊
Aren't you a surprise.
你千里迢迢赶来看这一幕 不是吗
You've come a long way to see this, haven't you?
来吧
Well, go ahead.
杀了我
Kill me.
杀你
Kill you?
你不认为那有点多此一举吗
Don't you think that would be a little…redundant?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你一定很痛苦地
It must be painful…
同穿着这身皮囊的我说话
Speaking to me in this…shape.
但是容器必须是你的弟弟
But it had to be your brother.
必须是
It had to be.
迪恩 你不必害怕我
You don't have to be afraid of me, dean.
你以为我会干什么
What do you think i'm going to do?
我不知道 也许毁了这个星球
I don't know. maybe deep-fry the planet?
为什么
Why?
我为什么要毁这美妙的星球
Why would I want to destroy this stunning thing…
炫彩斑斓
Beautiful in a trillion different ways…
上帝的最后一个完美杰作
The last perfect handiwork of god?
你从没听说过我是如何堕落的故事
You ever hear the story of how I fell from grace?
真不走运 你不是来告诉我该睡觉了
Oh, good god. you're not gonna tell me a bedtime.
我没什么胃口
My stomach's almost out of bile.
你知道上帝为什么丢下我么
You know why god cast me down?
因为我爱过他
Because I loved him.
胜过一切
More than anything.
于是上帝创造了…你
And then god created…you.
这毛还没长齐的小人物
The little…Hairless apes.
他告诉我们大家要听从你
And then he asked all of us to bow down before you …
比爱他更爱你
To love you more than him.
于是我说 「上帝…我做不到」
And I said, "father…I can't."
「这些人类是有缺点的 凶残的」
I said, "these human beings are flawed, murderous."
就这样…
And for that…
上帝让米伽勒把我丢到了地狱
God had michael cast me into hell.
现在你来告诉我…
Now, tell me…
这处罚对这罪行合适么
Does the punishment fit the crime?
尤其我还是对的
Especially when I was right?
看看你们这60亿人都为这事做过什么
Look at what 6 billion of you have done to this thing.
又有多少人为这事责怪我？
And how many of you blame me for it?
你不要愚弄我
You're not fooling me. you know that?
说这种同情邪恶的废话
With this sympathy-for-the-devil crap.
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
我是什么？
What am i?
你们是同类 只是你更大些儿
You're the same thing, only bigger.
如出一辙的小强
The same brand of cockroach.
我已经毁了我的一生
I've been squashing my whole life …
丑陋 邪恶 狡诈
An ugly, evil, belly-to-the-ground,
这都是他妈的扯蛋
Supernatural piece of crap.
你和他们唯一的区别就是
The only difference between them and you.
你自负
Is the size of your ego.
我喜欢你 迪恩
I like you, dean.
我知道有其他天使们看中了你
I get what the other angels see in you.
再见
Goodbye.
我们不久会再次见面的
We'll meet again soon.
你最好现在就杀了我
You better kill me now!
你说什么
Pardon?
你最好现在就杀了我
You better kill me now.
否则我发誓 我将会找到方法杀死你
Or I swear, I will find a way to kill you.
并且我不会停下来
And I won't stop.
我知道你不会
I know you won't.
我知道你也不会答应米伽勒
I know you won't say "yes" to michael, either.
而且我知道你不会杀死萨姆
And I know you won't kill sam.
无论你做什么
Whatever you do…
你将永远在这儿结束了
You will always end up here.
不管你是被选中 还是你改变细节
Whatever choices you make, whatever details you alter,
我们都将永远在这儿结束
We will always end up…here.
我赢了
I win.
是的 我赢了
So, I win.
你错了
You're wrong.
五年后来看你 迪恩
See you in five years, dean.
我真想对着耶稣说句去你妈的
Oh, well, if it isn't the ghost of christmas "screw you."
够了
Enough.
迪恩 够了
Dean, enough.
你看见了它 对么 你看见了发生了什么
You saw it, right? you saw what happens.
你是唯一能证明恶魔罪行的人
You're the only person who can prove the devil wrong.
只要说
Just say "yes."
我怎么知道这整个事情是不是
How do I know that this whole thing isn't one.
某个天使的骗局？
Huh? some angel hocus-pocus?
游戏时间结束了
The time for tricks is over.
把自己交给米伽勒
Give yourself to michael.
说“答应” 我们就可以进攻了
Say "yes, " and we can strike.
在路西法得到萨姆之前
Before lucifer gets to sam.
在众人死之前
Before billions die.
你在告诉我你还没吸取教训？
You telling me you haven't learned your lesson?
我已经吸取了教训
Oh, i've learned a lesson, all right.
只是不是你想教的那个
Just not the one you wanted to teach.
好吧 我只好不得不再教一次
Well, i'll just have to teach it again!
因为我现在就得到你了 孩子
Because I got you now, boy,
我不会让你
And i'm never letting you …
妈的
Son of a…
干得漂亮 卡西
That's pretty nice timing, cass.
我们有约定的
We had an appointment.
不会改变
Don't ever change.
撒迦利亚是怎么找到你的？
How did zachariah find you?
说来话长
Long story.
让我们从现在起就远离耶和华见证会 好吗？
Let's just stay away from jehovah's witnesses from now on, okay?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
首要我应该要做完的一些事
Something I should have done in the first place.
萨姆
Sam.
如果你是认真的 你也想回来…
If you're serious and you want back in…
你应该紧紧把握这个机会
…you should hang on to this.
我确信你已经没价值了
I'm sure you're rusty.
听着 兄弟 我很抱歉
Look, man, i'm sorry.
我不知道我需要做什么
I don't know. i'm…whatever I need to be.
但是我…
But I was, uh…
错了
Wrong.
是什么改变了你的想法
What made you change your mind?
说来话长
Long story.
重点是
The point is…
我们是彼此的致命点
Maybe we are each other's achilles' heel.
他们一定会找到利用我们对抗对方的方法
Maybe they'll find a way to use us against each other.
我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道我们是彼此拥有的一切
I just know we're all we've got.
胜过一切
More than that.
我们要保持彼此的人性
We keep each other human.
谢谢
Thank you.
真的很感谢
Really. thank you.
我不会让你堕落的
I won't let you down.
我知道
Oh, I know it.
我的意思是你是这世上第二棒的猎人
I mean, you are the second-best hunter on the planet.
那么 我们现在做什么？
So, what do we do now?
我们规划我们自己的未来
We make our own future.
我们别无选择
Guess we have no choice.